{"id": "search_qa_0", "question": "I'm tired of Cuisinart and grey pans, got anything else? Give me a product ID for a different brand and color.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_0", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Pan Set is designed primarily for creating individual or two-person servings, making it less suitable for the needs of preparing larger family meals where more servings are required.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_1", "question": "I'm not messing around with cheap brands. Give me a pan from Copper Chef or Lodge that can handle temperatures above 600F.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_1", "question": "Is the stainless steel pan resistant to warping when exposed to high heat?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_2", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of the T-fal Handy Pot?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this T-fal pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal fry pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this T-fal pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the T-fal fry pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_2", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 dollars and I only want either a black or green one. Give me the pan that matches these specifics.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_3", "question": "What is the depth measurement of the pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan designed to be dishwasher-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this pan designed to be dishwasher-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_4", "question": "Is the Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_5", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?", "long_answer": "The Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet can indeed be used to cook steaks to medium-rare or to any other level of doneness you prefer.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_6", "question": "Is the non-stick surface of this ceramic-coated pan resistant to damage from acidic foods when used according to the manufacturer's instructions?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it recommended to cook acidic foods in this pan before a good patina has been established?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for acidic sauces, given that it's not dishwasher safe?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it recommended to cook acidic foods in this pan before a good patina has been established?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this pan suitable for acidic sauces, given that it's not dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_7", "question": "Can the T-fal A8572494 saucepan be used for cooking on high heat?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_3", "question": "I gotta roast some veggies and need a pan that can stomach a solid 400F in the oven. Oh, and it's gotta be green, don't ask. Got anything like that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_0", "question": "I am in search of eco-friendly cookware. Do these pans align with that objective?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_1", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is it safe to prepare all kinds of food in this pan without concern for flavor changes?", "long_answer": "When you're thinking about using a cast iron pan, keep in mind that it's not suitable for all kinds of food. Cooking acidic dishes such as tomato sauce, for instance, can erode the seasoning of the pan and might lead to the food having a metallic flavor. Hence, it's best to steer clear of extensive cooking of acidic items in cast iron cookware.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron cannot be used for acidic foods like tomato sauce for extended periods, as the acid can strip the seasoning and cause the food to take on a metallic taste.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_2", "question": "Is this pan durable enough to handle frequent use for preparing various cuisines?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan designed to withstand repeated use for batch baking?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this pan designed to withstand repeated use for batch baking?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_8", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be versatile, making it suitable for use in various cooking techniques, including both baking and broiling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_9", "question": "What is the maximum oven-safe temperature for the Copper Chef pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_4", "question": "I got a soft spot for ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and Norpro, but I can't drop more than 30 dollars. What's the cheapest pan you have from either of those brands?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_3", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "long_answer": "Should low maintenance be a priority for you, it may be worthwhile to explore alternative options. This pan is not dishwasher-safe, necessitating additional upkeep including hand washing and regular re-seasoning to maintain its optimal performance over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance and may involve extra steps like re-seasoning or careful hand-polishing to uphold their performance and appearance standards.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_10", "question": "Is there a manufacturer warranty included with these pans?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are these pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are these pans dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_5", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 bucks for a pan, and it sure as hell ain't gonna be from Copper Chef. So, what's the largest pan you can offer for that price?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_4", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is this pan suitable for acidic sauces, given that it's not dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The design of the pan facilitates hand washing and offers advantages like effective heat retention, suitable for traditional cooking techniques. However, you should be aware of its potential reactivity with acidic ingredients. Depending on its material, taking additional precautions when cooking acidic dishes may be necessary to preserve the lifespan of the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are ideally used for traditional or specialized cooking methods that take advantage of their unique material properties, such as the heat retention of cast iron.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_11", "question": "Is the Anolon saucepan suitable for making candy that requires precise temperature control?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_12", "question": "What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_13", "question": "What type of warranty is included with the purchase of these pans?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are these pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are these pans dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_6", "question": "I'm all about the big guns when it comes to pans and I dig Anolon and Ozeri brands. Hook me up with the largest one they got that's over 10 inches.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_7", "question": "I'm in the market for a large pan, needs to be blue or silver, anything over 12 inches will do. But it's got to handle some heat, what's the highest oven-safe temperature pan you got in those colors?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_8", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, preferable in grey or black color, but I don't want it if it's from Tramontina. What's the biggest one you got that matches what I'm looking for?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_14", "question": "Does the pan's actual weight correspond to the listed weight of 2.6 pounds in the description?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_5", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "long_answer": "Should low maintenance be a priority for you, it may be prudent to explore alternative choices. This pan lacks a dishwasher-safe attribute, necessitating additional attention, including manual cleaning and regular re-seasoning, to maintain its optimal functionality over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance and may involve extra steps like re-seasoning or careful hand-polishing to uphold their performance and appearance standards.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_6", "question": "Is this pan designed to be presentable on a table setting?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan designed to be dishwasher-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this pan designed to be dishwasher-safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_15", "question": "Do users report any balance or weight distribution problems when handling these pans?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_7", "question": "Is it possible to utilize this pan for cooking on the stovetop as well as presenting food at the dining table?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for direct placement on charcoal during a barbecue?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this pan suitable for direct placement on charcoal during a barbecue?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_16", "question": "Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_17", "question": "Does the frying pan become non-stick following seasoning?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_18", "question": "Is the Tramontina pan compatible with gas cooktops and does it provide even heat distribution when used on them?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_19", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set features a construction of stainless steel, which provides the product with strength and enhances its durability for long-term use.", "short_answer": "stainless steel", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_20", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "long_answer": "The general consensus among customers is that the pan is sturdy and durable, with a significant number of users reporting that it lasts for many years without issues.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_9", "question": "I'm a big fan of Lodge, what's the cheapest pan they have in your store?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_10", "question": "I'm looking to add a pop of color to my kitchen. Do you have any blue pans in your product line?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_8", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Can this pan withstand frequent washing if I regularly run my kitchenware through the dishwasher?", "long_answer": "Certainly. This pan is designed to withstand frequent usage. It's crafted to be resilient against extreme heat and the harsh chemicals found in dishwasher detergents, ensuring it remains resistant to warping, rusting, or deterioration, even when subjected to daily cycles in the dishwasher.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_9", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan, or is it better to refrain from doing so?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_21", "question": "Can the tempered-glass lid be used with different sizes and brands of cookware?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_22", "question": "Can the heavy-gauge, hard-anodized aluminum saucepan be used on a glass top range?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_23", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "long_answer": "The pan is confirmed to be oven safe and can safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit (232 degrees Celsius). However, it should not be used under the broiler as it is not designed to handle the direct intense heat of that setting.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_10", "question": "Is it acceptable to clean this pan using only soap and water, or does it have specific cleaning instructions?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_24", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Cuisinart saucepan is particularly designed to handle high-heat cooking applications, including but not limited to rolling boils and the reduction of liquids, both of which require the pan to be subjected to high temperatures.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_11", "question": "I'm a bit of a home chef, and I need a pan that can withstand the heat. What's the top pan you have from either Presto or Tramontina that can handle over 400F in the oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_11", "question": "I'm in search of sustainable cookware options. Would purchasing these pans align with that objective?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_12", "question": "I do a lot of high-heat cooking, so I need a pan that can handle at least 400F and is larger than the average size. What's the best option you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_25", "question": "Can using cooking spray damage non-stick cookware surfaces?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_26", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?", "long_answer": "The exterior of the pan is constructed to be durable; however, it may display signs of wear and discoloration over time, particularly after heavy usage and consistent exposure to high temperatures.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_27", "question": "Is the T-fal pan compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_12", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the pan is also safe for use in broiling. The stainless steel lid can withstand the high temperatures of a broiler without suffering damage. Nonetheless, ensure that if the pan handle is not constructed of stainless steel, it too can withstand the broiler's extreme heat.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid are ideally used for oven recipes due to their high heat tolerance, provided that the handle is also oven-safe if it is not made from stainless steel.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_13", "question": "I need a new pan, but I'm a loyal Presto fan and my wallet can't handle anything north of 20 dollars. You got anything that ain't gonna break the bank?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_14", "question": "Listen, I've had enough of Norpro. Get me the most affordable pan from another brand that can handle at least 450 degrees in the oven.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_28", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is the pan suitable for baking submarine sandwich loaves?", "long_answer": "Customers report success with the pan when baking a variety of bread types, which includes the making of submarine sandwich loaves, indicating its versatility in bread-making.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_29", "question": "Can the Stone Earth Frying Pan's non-stick coating withstand the use of acidic ingredients such as tomato sauce without damage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it advisable to frequently cook acidic foods such as tomato sauce in this pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for acidic sauces, given that it's not dishwasher safe?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it advisable to frequently cook acidic foods such as tomato sauce in this pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this pan suitable for acidic sauces, given that it's not dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_30", "question": "What is the duration and type of warranty provided with the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan designed to withstand repeated use for batch baking?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this pan designed to withstand repeated use for batch baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_31", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is this T-fal pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The T-fal pan is designed to be dishwasher safe, enabling easy cleaning. Despite this, it is advisable to hand wash the pan in order to extend the durability of the nonstick coating, as frequent dishwasher use could potentially reduce its lifespan and effectiveness.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_32", "question": "What type of protection is included with the pans for storage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_15", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's bigger than 8 inches, doesn't cost more than 20 dollars, and can handle some heat in the oven. Give me your best option.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_16", "question": "I'm trying to save some money and can’t afford anything over 10 dollars. What's the cheapest pan you have?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_33", "question": "Does the non-stick coating on this pan maintain its durability over time with proper use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_34", "question": "Are use and care instructions included with the purchase of this cast iron skillet for first-time users?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_35", "question": "Are replacement parts available for purchase for the Presto 5900 Electric Wok, like new legs or a glass lid?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the electric wok designed with rounded sides identical to traditional woks?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the electric wok designed with rounded sides identical to traditional woks?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_17", "question": "I ain't too impressed with Ozeri, so show me some other brand's pan that's at least 10 inches. And no funny business, show me the first one you find.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_36", "question": "Is this pan compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_13", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "long_answer": "Indeed, because the pan is not dishwasher safe, it may need to be polished to maintain its look, along with routine upkeep such as seasoning, based on the material, to avoid aesthetic degradation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" do not have a function of self-maintenance and will need regular seasoning (for cast iron or carbon steel) or polishing (for aesthetic reasons) to maintain their best condition.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_37", "question": "Is the red Thermo-Spot on the cookware designed to maintain its color over time with regular use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will the finish on this pan deteriorate if it goes through frequent dishwashing cycles?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will the finish on this pan deteriorate if it goes through frequent dishwashing cycles?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_38", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "long_answer": "The cooking surface of the product is designed to be non-stick and customer feedback suggests it performs well initially. Nevertheless, over time, the effectiveness of the non-stick feature may diminish, and it is essential to follow proper maintenance guidelines to sustain its non-stick quality for as long as possible.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_14", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is this pan ready for immediate use on an induction cooktop straight from the packaging?", "long_answer": "Should you be interested in our aluminum or copper frying pans or skillets, be aware that they are not compatible with magnetic induction, which is crucial for induction cooktops. To use them on these types of stoves, you will need an extra ferrous disc to facilitate the required magnetic response for heating.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_18", "question": "Look, I'm not shelling out more than 30 dollars for a pan but it's gotta be larger than 12 inches. What's the best option you got for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_39", "question": "How does the weight of these die-cast aluminum pans compare to cast iron pans for handling?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_40", "question": "Are the pans in the Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_19", "question": "I'm trying to match my kitchen decor and I want a big, blue pan. What's the cheapest one you got that's 12 inches or bigger?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_41", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does the product's nonstick coating contain PFOA?", "long_answer": "The product is equipped with a high-performance reinforced nonstick coating that is free from PFOA, thereby providing a safer cooking experience and facilitating easy cleanup.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_42", "question": "Are customers generally satisfied with the non-stick quality of this product?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_43", "question": "Is this product compatible with induction cooktops as well as other types of cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_44", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?", "long_answer": "The product metadata does not detail whether measurement marks are present on the interior of the pot, and reviews do not frequently mention this feature, thus it is not possible to confirm that the pot comes with interior measurement markings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_20", "question": "I don't want any black pan, and it needs to handle at least 450F. What's the cheapest option does your store offer?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_45", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?", "long_answer": "The ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan is constructed with a robust aluminum core, which ensures even heating and serves to resist warping. Customer feedback indicates that warping is not a common problem with this pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_21", "question": "Look, I gotta avoid grey, but I'm keen on either Presto or Bialetti brands for pans. Which can tolerate the highest oven heat from these specific brands?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_46", "question": "Is the pan lighter or heavier compared to similar cookware products?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_47", "question": "Does the non-stick surface of the pan maintain its performance over time with proper care?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_15", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "long_answer": "To preserve the condition of the pan's surface, refrain from using harsh detergents or abrasive scrubbing tools that may mar the anodized aluminum. For best results, employ a gentle touch, cleaning with a soft sponge or cloth to maintain the pan's non-stick and non-reactive qualities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_48", "question": "Does the pan's ergonomic handle successfully ease the handling of the pan's weight?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_49", "question": "Is the Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_50", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is crafted from high-quality stainless steel, which allows for its use both on the stovetop and in the oven, indicating its oven-safe properties.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_51", "question": "Are the silicone-coated handles of cookware resistant to high temperatures?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_52", "question": "Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be safely placed in an oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_22", "question": "I don't have a lot of dough to spend, but I need a Utopia Kitchen pan that won't cost more than 30 dollars and can handle high oven temperatures. What's the best one you've got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_23", "question": "I don't want a Tramontina, show me the cheapest alternative you have in your pan range.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_24", "question": "I'm hunting for a black pan. Preferably All-Clad or USA Pan. Which one of those can withstand the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_53", "question": "Do the pot's handles provide comfort and safety when handling?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_54", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is this pan designed to withstand repeated use for batch baking?", "long_answer": "The pan's capacity to bake 12 items simultaneously, alongside its durability and ease of cleanup, suggests that it is suitable for repeated use when batch baking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_25", "question": "I'm not messing around anymore with pans that warp under high heat. Which one of your pans can handle temperatures of over 500 degrees Fahrenheit? Give me the first one you get.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_55", "question": "Does cooking with this wok provide energy savings compared to using a traditional stove?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_56", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is this pan designed to be dishwasher-safe?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be dishwasher-safe, allowing for convenient cleaning. However, to maintain the non-stick surface and the exterior finish in optimal condition, hand-washing is recommended over machine washing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_57", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this cast iron skillet without scratching it?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_16", "question": "I frequently encounter issues with pans failing to heat uniformly on my stove. Does this design assist in promoting even heat distribution?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_26", "question": "I've got a thing against All-Clad and I'm dead set on grey. Show me the first pan that you've got that fits that description.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_58", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "long_answer": "The frying pan is sold as a single item, and the product metadata does not specify the inclusion of any accessories, implying that a lid or spatula is not provided with the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_59", "question": "Is a metal spatula suitable for use with this non-stick pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_60", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?", "long_answer": "Unlike cast iron cookware, the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan is made from stainless steel, which does not need seasoning to create a non-stick surface or to maintain its quality over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_61", "question": "What is the weight characteristic of this pan as reported by users?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_27", "question": "Look, I don't have more than 10 bucks and I only trust Copper Chef and Ozeri. Find me a pan from one of those brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_62", "question": "What is the composition material of the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_28", "question": "I'm looking for a pan, either copper or green, that can handle high temperatures. Which one can withstand the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_63", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart French Classic Pan is technically dishwasher safe, but to extend the life of the non-stick coating and the pan itself, hand washing with a mild detergent is recommended.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_29", "question": "I'm doing a lot of big batch cooking these days and I need a big pan that can handle high oven heat. What's the best pan you have that's at least 12 inches and can withstand the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_30", "question": "I'm tired of those usual silver pans. Find me the biggest pan you have, just make sure it's not silver.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_31", "question": "I'm only interested in Matfer Bourgeat or Ozeri brand pans. Can you find me the cheapest one from these brands?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_64", "question": "Can the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set accommodate servings for two individuals?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_32", "question": "I've been cooking with Norpro pans for years now, but they're just not heat resistant enough sometimes. Can you tell me what's their highest temperature-safe pan you carry?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_33", "question": "I'm tired of the usual black pans and I'm not a fan of Lodge's stuff. What's the first alternative you can offer?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_65", "question": "Does the Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet come already seasoned?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_66", "question": "Is it necessary to cook with oil or butter when using the ZWILLING Spirit ceramic non-stick pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_34", "question": "Look, I don't want to spend more than 30 dollars, and I need a pan that can handle heat above 600F. What's my cheapest option?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_67", "question": "Is the pan suitable for preparing meals that serve more than two people?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I am in search of a multifunctional pan capable of both simmering soups and handling frying tasks. Would this be an appropriate choice for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I am in search of a multifunctional pan capable of both simmering soups and handling frying tasks. Would this be an appropriate choice for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_68", "question": "Is this pot of appropriate size for preparing pasta dishes for a small to medium-sized family?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_69", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the T-fal fry pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The T-fal fry pan is designed to be dishwasher safe, allowing for convenient and easy cleaning without the need for manual washing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_70", "question": "Is this fry pan compatible with an electric glass top stove?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_35", "question": "I'm looking for a grey pan that can stand up to heat. Can you find me one that's above your average oven safe temperature, but keep it cheap?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_71", "question": "What is the country of origin for the final assembly of these pans with a GREBLON ceramic coating?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}, {"question": "Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_72", "question": "Does the Thermo-Spot heat indicator on the pan reliably indicate when the pan is sufficiently pre-heated?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_17", "question": "Can this pan evenly cook my food, particularly during meat searing?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_73", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to clean the frying pan in a dishwasher because doing so could damage its seasoning. To properly maintain the pan, it should be hand washed using hot water, and if needed, scrubbed with a brush.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_36", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that can withstand the heat of at least 450F and doesn't cost me more than 20 dollars. What's the largest one you have?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_37", "question": "I'm sticking to a tight budget but still want quality. Give me the biggest pan you have from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels or USA Pan under $10.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_38", "question": "I ain't got more than 10 dollars. And my oven works like a blast furnace. So, could you find me an all-purpose pan that can withstand a temperature of over 600F and costs 10 bucks or less?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_74", "question": "Is the 1 1/2 quart saucepan large enough to accommodate larger canned items?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_75", "question": "Does the non-stick performance of the pan degrade after a month of use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_76", "question": "What is the volume capacity, in quarts, of this saucepan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_77", "question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_78", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?", "long_answer": "The Madeleine Pan is an excellent choice as a gift, particularly for those with an affinity for baking or for individuals who are interested in beginning to bake.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_79", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with the non-stick surface of this pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_18", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "long_answer": "Our frying pans and skillets, crafted from aluminum or copper, boast superior heat conductivity that ensures even cooking. Nevertheless, should you use an induction stove, bear in mind that these materials lack inherent compatibility because they do not possess magnetic properties. Consequently, cooking performance may suffer unless you employ a ferrous plate to enable induction.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_39", "question": "I'm a fan of Presto and Chicago Metallic. Point me to the first pan you have from either of these brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_80", "question": "Is the Copper Chef pan resistant to tarnishing and oxidation compared to traditional copper pans?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_40", "question": "I always crank my oven up pretty high, like beyond 400F, and I want my pans in blue. Got anything that can handle all that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_81", "question": "What is the duration of the warranty provided for the T-fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_82", "question": "Is the bottom of the frying pans designed to prevent oil from pooling at the sides?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_41", "question": "I don't need any blue pans and I'm cooking for a large group, so it needs to be bigger than 8 inches. What's the first thing you'd recommend?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_83", "question": "Is the Stone Earth Pan compatible with induction stoves for cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_42", "question": "Cooking at high temperatures is my game. Get me the cheapest pan that can take the heat over 500F.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_19", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is unsuitable for cooking techniques such as blackening fish that demand very high temperatures. Owing to its aluminum make-up, this pan lacks the high heat resistance of alternatives like cast iron or stainless steel, which are preferred for such methods.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's lack of high heat tolerance lack the capability to withstand searing and broiling applications that require maintaining structural integrity at very high temperatures, unlike cookware made of materials like stainless steel or cast iron.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_84", "question": "Is the cookware's handle designed to remain cool during cooking, and does it come with additional heat protection?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_43", "question": "I'm a loyal fan of Chicago Metallic, but I ain't paying more than 20 dollars. What's the cheapest pan you got from them?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_44", "question": "Listen, I'm picky about colors. You got any pans in either grey or blue? Just show me the first one that fits the criteria.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_20", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for roasting a chicken?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_45", "question": "I have a strict requirement for oven-safe temperature to be at least 450°F and anything but green. What's the first pan you can recommend?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_21", "question": "Is it safe to use my metal spatula with this pan without causing any damage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_46", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 dollars and I need a pan that's at least 12 inches. Can you find me a deal like that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_47", "question": "I don't want to pay more than the average price and I really like copper color. Seriously, show me the first pan you’ve got that meets my criteria.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_48", "question": "I do a lot of high temp cooking and only use Norpro gadgets. Do you have any pans that can take at least 500F? What's the ID of the product that can do this?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_49", "question": "I am not a fan of green and my cooking usually requires high heat. Which pan can withstand an oven temperature over 600F but isn't green?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_50", "question": "I'm after a pan that's either grey or copper, and I'm not interested in breaking the bank. Can you find me the cheapest one you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_51", "question": "I need a new pan, but I want it to be bigger than 12 inches and either green or blue. What's the cheapest one you got in those specifications?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_52", "question": "I ain't gonna throw over 30 dollars for a pan. Find me the biggest heckin' one in the budget.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_53", "question": "I'm after a Matfer Bourgeat pan but don't have more than 50 bucks to drop. Get me the highest oven-safe one within my budget.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_54", "question": "I plan on using my pan in the oven at pretty high temp, over 600 degrees, and I have a thing for copper or silver. What's the product that matches these preferences?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_85", "question": "Is the saucepan available for purchase within a cookware set offered by Anolon?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_22", "question": "Is this pan capable of retaining moisture while cooking vegetables to prevent them from becoming dry?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_55", "question": "I need a reliable All-Clad pan that can withstand over 400F in the oven. What's the first one you've got that can take the heat?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_56", "question": "I'm a big fan of \"Copper Chef\", and I'm looking for a pan that's bigger than average size. Also, I need it to handle high temperatures in the oven. Got anything like that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_86", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "long_answer": "Seasoning the pan is not required before its initial use since it comes with a non-stick ceramic coating that is ready for cooking straight from the packaging.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_57", "question": "I'm a big fan of Bialetti, and I'm currently looking for the largest pan they've got. Which one is it?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_87", "question": "Is it advisable to use cooking sprays on the nonstick surface of the pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_58", "question": "I'm a big fan of Norpro, but I'm looking specifically for a pan that can stand a temperature above 450F in the oven. Can you find that for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_59", "question": "I like my pans to handle some heat in the oven, at least 400F, and they gotta be bigger than 8 inches. What's the most affordable one you got that meets these requirements?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_60", "question": "Look, I'm after a really good pan but it's gotta be either blue or copper, just not Bialetti. Got anything that can handle the highest temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_23", "question": "Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_24", "question": "Do I require specialized cleaning agents for the pan to maintain its like-new appearance?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_88", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?", "long_answer": "Cast iron cookware is favored by many because it does not have synthetic coatings that could potentially release harmful chemicals. Additionally, cooking with cast iron has a health advantage as it can impart a small but significant amount of iron to the food prepared in it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_89", "question": "Does the pan's design include a raised center that could lead to uneven cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_61", "question": "I'm not a fan of Ozeri at all. Which pan from any other brand can withstand the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_62", "question": "I'm looking for a silver Presto pan, but I don't want to break the bank. What's the cheapest one you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_90", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan without damaging its surface?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_91", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "long_answer": "Cooking with stainless steel cookware typically requires medium heat to prevent food from sticking and to protect the pan's surface. It's crucial to consult the manufacturer's instructions for optimal cooking temperatures and methods for the specific cookware.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_25", "question": "I like to blacken fish; will this pan suffice for such cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_63", "question": "I'm pretty particular about the brands I use in my kitchen. Get me the first product you have from either Anolon or All-Clad.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_64", "question": "I don't want to splurge but I'm a fan of All-Clad. Could you suggest a pan that doesn't cost more than 50 dollars from All-Clad?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_65", "question": "I like to bake in high temperatures, and I need something sizable. What's the biggest pan you have that can withstand more than 600F in the oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_92", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?", "long_answer": "The pan is specifically crafted for Madeleines; however, thanks to its non-stick surface, it can be also used to bake other desserts that are comparable in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_66", "question": "I'm only interested in Tramontina and All-Clad pans. Find me the cheapest one from these brands, will ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_93", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is this saucepan dishwasher-safe?", "long_answer": "The saucepan should be hand-washed for optimal care since it is not suitable for cleaning in a dishwasher because of its nonstick coating.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_67", "question": "I'm in the market for a new pan and I'm considering either All-Clad or Matfer Bourgeat, but only in either a copper or black color. Give me the first pan you find that matches those requirements.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_68", "question": "I'm in need of a pan that can handle some serious heat, over 450F, and I only do black or silver in my kitchen. What's the best you got for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_94", "question": "Are the legs of this wok stand sturdy and durable for normal home use despite some users reporting issues over time?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Could the pan rust if it's not maintained correctly?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Could the pan rust if it's not maintained correctly?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_95", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it recommended to cook acidic foods in this pan before a good patina has been established?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to cook highly acidic foods in the pan until a very good patina has been established, as doing so may strip the seasoning off the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_69", "question": "I need a pan from the brand Chicago Metallic, but I don't wanna burn more than 10 dollars for this. Can you find any for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_96", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The pan should not be placed in a dishwasher as this could damage its seasoning and reduce its lifespan. Hand washing without soap is the best method for cleaning to preserve the pan's quality.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_70", "question": "I'm after a cheap pan that can handle some serious heat, at least 500 degrees. Find me something solid for under 30 dollars, will you?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_97", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the electric wok designed with rounded sides identical to traditional woks?", "long_answer": "The electric wok bears resemblance to traditional woks with rounded sides; however, it is engineered with a flat bottom to support the electric heating element, providing a slightly altered cooking experience when compared to authentic round-bottomed woks.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_98", "question": "Is the heavy-gauge aluminum pan capable of distributing heat evenly?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_99", "question": "Does the riveted silicone handle on this cookware maintain a cool temperature during use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_100", "question": "Does the pot feature a non-stick surface on both the interior and exterior?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_101", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "long_answer": "The pan should be used on low to medium heat in accordance with the manufacturer's guidelines in order to preserve the non-stick surface. Using the pan on high heat could potentially damage the surface and may also void the warranty.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_102", "question": "Is it recommended to store food in the refrigerator using these non-stick pans?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are these pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are these pans dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_103", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it advisable to frequently cook acidic foods such as tomato sauce in this pan?", "long_answer": "Cooking acidic foods like tomato sauce in this pan is generally not advised, as they can damage the seasoned layer on the pan's surface. If the seasoning is lost, it requires reapplication to restore the pan's non-stick properties.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_26", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "It is recommended to avoid using metal utensils on this pan because it is constructed from ceramic material that is prone to scratching or chipping when exposed to such implements. Doing so could impair its non-stick properties and reduce the pan's longevity.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with ceramic material lack the capability to endure the use of metal utensils, as such tools can scratch or chip the non-stick surface and diminish the pan's lifespan.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "ceramic", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_71", "question": "I need a pan of at least 8 inches that can take more heat than your average pan. What's the first one you got that suits this?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_72", "question": "I can't spend tons on cookware, and I need a pan that withstands at least the average oven safe temperature, but costs under 20 dollars. Can you find one for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_73", "question": "Listen, I only have 20 bucks to spend on a pan and I only trust Anolon or ZWILLING J.A. Henckels. So what's the best option you got for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_27", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is it safe to wash this pan in the dishwasher without concern for gradual damage?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this pan is crafted to endure the elevated heat and potent detergents typical of dishwashers, maintaining its integrity and appearance over successive washing cycles without succumbing to warping, corrosion, or deterioration.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_28", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "long_answer": "To preserve the surface integrity of this pan, steer clear of abrasive cleaning agents or scrubbing pads that might scratch the anodized aluminum. It's advisable to clean gently with a soft sponge or cloth to maintain the pan's non-reactive and non-stick characteristics.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_104", "question": "Is there a lifetime warranty on the Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_74", "question": "I'm only interested in black or silver pans and I need it to withstand a pretty high oven temperature. Can you find me the baking pan that fits this criteria?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_75", "question": "Look, I need a pan that won't break the bank, and it's gotta be bigger than your average size. Also, I need it to survive some serious oven time. Show me the one that ticks all these boxes.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_76", "question": "I'm trying to save a few bucks here and I need a pan that can stand heat up to 400F. Can you fetch me the cheapest option you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_105", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is constructed from stainless steel, which is not a nonstick material. To reduce the likelihood of food sticking to the pan, it is recommended to spray the pan with cooking oil before use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_29", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "long_answer": "Round-shaped pans are not the most space-efficient for storage in tight kitchens, which may be a disadvantage if maximizing every inch is essential. Square or angular pans might fit better if you need to tuck them into a small cupboard or shelf.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_106", "question": "Is cooking spray suitable for use with a Tramontina nonstick pan, or is cooking oil the better option?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_107", "question": "Is greasing the pan necessary when using a pan with a high-quality non-stick coating for baking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_30", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?", "long_answer": "This specific pan requires special attention, as it is not safe for dishwasher cleaning. Post-cooking, it must be hand-washed using proper methods and promptly dried to avoid damage. Should you prefer not to dedicate time to such maintenance routinely, consider opting for a dishwasher-safe pan instead.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are not recommended for use by consumers who may not be willing or able to invest the time and effort into the careful maintenance these pans require, which includes correct hand-washing techniques and immediate drying to prevent damage.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_77", "question": "I'm not made of money, I need a pan for my cluttered kitchen without breaking the bank. Can you show me the largest one you got for 20 dollars or less?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_78", "question": "I've got a beef with T-fal, so omit them. Show me the cheapest pan you got under 50 bucks.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this T-fal pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this T-fal pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_108", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?", "long_answer": "The stainless-steel cooking surface of the pan is non-reactive, ensuring that it does not alter the flavors of the food by imparting a metallic taste during cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_79", "question": "I'm no Rockefeller - I can't shell out more than 30 bucks. However, I need a pan that can stand up to high oven temperatures over 400F. Gimme the biggest one you got that fits that criteria.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_80", "question": "I don't want any pans from USA Pan and it's gotta be bigger than 8 inches. Just show me one that fits the criteria, okay?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_31", "question": "While simmering, I frequently face the challenge of adding water regularly to prevent burning. Can this pan assist in addressing that problem?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I am in search of a multifunctional pan capable of both simmering soups and handling frying tasks. Would this be an appropriate choice for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I am in search of a multifunctional pan capable of both simmering soups and handling frying tasks. Would this be an appropriate choice for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_109", "question": "Does baking bread goods in a heavy pan affect the evenness of heat distribution?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_110", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the saucepan's nonstick coating contain the harmful chemical PFOA?", "long_answer": "The saucepan utilizes Dupont's Autograph nonstick coating that is professional in quality, both inside and out, and is specifically designed to be free from PFOA, ensuring its safety for use in cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_111", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?", "long_answer": "The wok is found to be effective for traditional stir-frying by the majority of users. However, due to the heating element being concentrated at the bottom, it requires continuous movement of ingredients to achieve even cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_81", "question": "I'm in need of a big pan that can take some serious heat in the oven. Pull up the first pan you got that's over 10 inches and can handle temperatures above 400 F.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_32", "question": "Do I need to purchase any extra cleaning supplies when I buy this pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_112", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set compatible with the size of a standard toaster oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_113", "question": "Is the pan considered convenient for storage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_114", "question": "Does the T-fal pot contain any harmful toxins in its materials or non-stick coating?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the saucepan's nonstick coating contain the harmful chemical PFOA?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the product's nonstick coating contain PFOA?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the saucepan's nonstick coating contain the harmful chemical PFOA?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the product's nonstick coating contain PFOA?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_82", "question": "I'm looking for a grey or black pan that can withstand a high heat in the oven - up to 600F. Can you find one for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_115", "question": "Do customers consider the Spirit Fry Pan's weight to be easily manageable?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_83", "question": "I don't have a ton of cash to splash and I'm not a fan of Tramontina. So, which is the largest pan you have under 50 dollars from a different brand?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_84", "question": "I'm fixed on brands like Copper Chef and Norpro and I would prefer a silver or copper colored pan. Which product do you have that matches these specifications?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_33", "question": "Is it simple to recycle this cookware when it needs replacing?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan dishwasher safe?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_116", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are these pans dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The pans should preferably be washed by hand using a soft sponge and mild detergent in order to preserve the non-stick surface's quality, rather than being cleaned in a dishwasher.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_85", "question": "I'm not dropping more than 50 bucks on a pan, got it? Now show me the Utopia Kitchen or Copper Chef one that can withstand the highest temperature.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_117", "question": "Can the Copper Chef pan be used on an induction cooktop?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it possible to use this pan immediately on an induction cooktop without any prior preparation?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it possible to use this pan immediately on an induction cooktop without any prior preparation?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_86", "question": "No offense, but I don't want any of those Matfer Bourgeat pans. Can you find me the largest pan you have from any other brand?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_87", "question": "Look, I only got a tenner to spend and I'm looking for a pan in either copper or grey color. What options do I have?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_118", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?", "long_answer": "The wok is capable of achieving the high temperatures required for searing meats, provided that it is adequately preheated and the temperature is managed appropriately throughout the cooking process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_119", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "long_answer": "While the pan has a non-stick coating aimed at easy removal of cakes, it is recommended by some bakers to lightly grease the pan for a guaranteed effortless release of the Madeleines.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_88", "question": "I'm a bit of an amateur chef and I only trust USA Pan and Lodge pans. Which one of their products can stand the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_120", "question": "Can the Stone Earth Pan safely be used in an oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_121", "question": "How does the nonstick performance of All-Clad pans compare to that of other brands in terms of food release and ease of cleaning?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_122", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan cannot be used on induction cooktops because its construction material is aluminum, and aluminum is not a magnetic metal required to work with induction stoves.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_123", "question": "How user-friendly is the maintenance of the mirror polish on the pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_124", "question": "Can these pans be used on an induction cooktop without issues?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it possible to use this pan immediately on an induction cooktop without any prior preparation?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it possible to use this pan immediately on an induction cooktop without any prior preparation?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_34", "question": "Is this pan designed to be presentable for table service?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for baking submarine sandwich loaves?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for baking submarine sandwich loaves?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_125", "question": "Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_89", "question": "I ain't got tons of cash to splash and I need my pan to handle a hot oven. Show me the cheapest pan you got that can take 400F and still costs less than 10 dollars.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_126", "question": "Is the saucepan designed for easy hand cleaning?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this saucepan dishwasher-safe?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan dishwasher-safe?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_90", "question": "I'm not about to ruin a good pan in a hot oven and my wallet can't take a hit over 30 dollars. Show me your cheapest heat-resistant pan, safe for at least 500 degrees.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_91", "question": "I need a sturdy pan that can take the heat above 400F and comes in either silver or blue. What's the largest one you've got in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_92", "question": "I'm whipping up dishes that require some serious heat, above 450F. What's the largest pan you got that can handle that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_93", "question": "I got a big family to feed, need a pan at least 8 inches. Can you find me one that can handle the highest oven temperature?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_127", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils on this fry pan's nonstick interior?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_94", "question": "I need a pan that's at least 12 inches, but I didn't have a good experience with Tramontina. Show me the one with the highest oven-safe temperature you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_95", "question": "I'm cooking for a lot of guests. I need a big pan, atleast 12 inches. Also, the color should be either blue or copper. Can you help me find one?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_128", "question": "Is the Bialetti 6168 Fry Pan compatible with a ceramic glass stovetop without causing scratches?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_96", "question": "I ain't looking to spend a fortune, but I need a pan that can withstand a 600F oven and doesn't cost more than 20 dollars. What's the biggest one you got that fits the bill?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_97", "question": "I want a blue pan but nothing from Matfer Bourgeat. Gimme what you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}, {"question": "Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_129", "question": "Does the Presto 5900 Electric Wok perform comparably to a gas burner for stir-frying?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_35", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "long_answer": "While cooking with a cast iron skillet, it's best to limit the duration of cooking acidic foods. Acids may interact with the cast iron, eroding the essential seasoning layer that provides flavor and non-stick capabilities, and potentially giving your food a metallic flavor. Conversely, non-acidic foods can be prepared in the skillet without any issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron cannot be used for acidic foods like tomato sauce for extended periods, as the acid can strip the seasoning and cause the food to take on a metallic taste.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_98", "question": "I'm looking for a high-quality pan. It needs to be oven safe up to at least 400F and bigger than 12 inches. What's the best option you've got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_130", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "While the non-stick ceramic coated pans are advertised as easy to clean, it is advised to hand wash them in order to prolong the life of the non-stick coating and maintain their condition over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_99", "question": "I'm looking to do some high heat cooking, so I need a pan that can take at least 500F. And no green ones, please. What's the best you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_100", "question": "Look, I'm a fan of Lodge and frequently cook at high temperatures. Show me a pan from Lodge that can withstand more than 600F in the oven.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_131", "question": "Is the T-fal Specialty Nonstick pot available for purchase as a standalone item rather than as a component of a larger set?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_101", "question": "I'm looking for the largest pan either from Utopia Kitchen or Lodge, but nothing copper. Brass tacks - what's my best option?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_132", "question": "How does the quality of the USA Pan compare to pans from high-end baking stores?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_36", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?", "long_answer": "No, frequent dishwashing will not diminish the finish. The pans are crafted from sturdy metals with durable coatings or are anodized, designed to withstand the rigors of dishwashing and preserve their quality appearance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_133", "question": "Does this pan have a safe non-stick coating that prevents chemical exposure?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the saucepan's nonstick coating contain the harmful chemical PFOA?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the saucepan's nonstick coating contain the harmful chemical PFOA?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_134", "question": "What is the shape of the base of the wok, and is it appropriate for use on an electric heating element?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the electric wok designed with rounded sides identical to traditional woks?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the electric wok designed with rounded sides identical to traditional woks?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_37", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for dishes requiring frequent temperature adjustments?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_135", "question": "Is the All-Clad E785S264 frying pan set compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_136", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat as doing so can damage the nonstick coating and consequently diminish the saucepan's longevity. The saucepan is durable but to maintain its nonstick properties and overall integrity, it's best to avoid high-temperature cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_102", "question": "I don't need any small pans. Give me a big one, at least 8 inches, and it better be a USA Pan or Cuisinart. What's the first product you find?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_103", "question": "I've got a pretty picky kitchen color scheme here, and I need a blue pan that can handle at least 400F in the oven. Got anything like that in your store?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_137", "question": "Is the pan's design conducive to balanced weight distribution for easy tossing and flipping?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_104", "question": "I'm doing some heavy cooking and need an All-Clad pan that can handle more than 500°F. Which one would you suggest?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_105", "question": "I do a lot of heavy-duty cooking and need a pan that's at least 10 inches and can stand a temperature of over 500F. What's the best one you have got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_106", "question": "No more than 50 bucks and I want something bigger than 8 inches. Find me the pan that can take the most heat.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_107", "question": "I'm specifically looking for a bigger pan, over 8 inches, from ZWILLING J.A Henckels. Give me the cheapest option you have.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_138", "question": "Are the cookware handles resistant to high temperatures during stovetop use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_108", "question": "I'm in need of a pan that's at least 12 inches, but not a fan of the color blue. Gimme the first option you have that matches my criteria.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_139", "question": "Does the pan's non-stick surface work as advertised?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_140", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_141", "question": "Is the GREBLON ceramic coating on cookware safe from releasing toxic chemicals when used at high temperatures?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_38", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is it acceptable to use a steel wool scrubber to eliminate persistent food remnants from this pan?", "long_answer": "It is not advisable to use a steel wool scrubber on this pan. Since the pan is constructed from aluminum and might feature a non-stick coating or be anodized, abrasive cleaning pads such as steel wool could harm the finish and impair its non-stick capabilities.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's specific maintenance needs fail to meet the requirements for indiscriminate cleaning methods such as harsh scouring pads or certain dishwasher detergents, especially if they have a non-stick layer or are anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_109", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's either black or grey and from either Utopia Kitchen or Chicago Metallic. Just show me one.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_142", "question": "Is the French Classic Tri-Ply product line manufactured in France?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the product's nonstick coating contain PFOA?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Does the product's nonstick coating contain PFOA?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_143", "question": "Is it safe to cook with high heat using this nonstick pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_144", "question": "Are T-fal Professional fry pans compatible with metal utensils without losing their nonstick properties?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the T-fal fry pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the T-fal fry pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_110", "question": "I'm a Presto fan, but I'm not made of money. What's the cheapest pan you've got from them?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_39", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it safe to routinely wash this pan in my dishwasher without causing any harm to it?", "long_answer": "Certainly, you may confidently wash this pan in your dishwasher. Our pans are crafted using robust materials such as stainless steel and aluminum, ensuring they can endure the intense conditions of a dishwasher without compromise.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_111", "question": "Look, I've got 30 dollars to drop on a pan. I want a decent size though, no mini pans or anything. Find me the cheapest pan that's at least the average size out there.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_145", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "long_answer": "The pan is regarded as suitable for high-heat cooking methods, such as searing, provided that it is adequately preheated, as confirmed by the majority of customers who have experienced its even heat distribution.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_112", "question": "I don't want to drop more than 50 dollars and I'm only interested in Anolon. What's the cheapest pan you got from them?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_113", "question": "I'm over the basic black, and I need a pan that's larger than 12 inches. What's the first colorful one you can find for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_114", "question": "I'm not the biggest fan of silver pans. Can you find me a pan that's either from Cuisinart or Anolon but absolutely not silver?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_146", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is indeed made from stainless steel, which provides durability and longevity for the cookware.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_147", "question": "Is it advisable to wash these nonstick pans in a dishwasher?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are these pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan dishwasher safe?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are these pans dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_115", "question": "I often crank up my oven to 400 degrees, and I only trust Utopia Kitchen and Ozeri. What's the first pan that can handle that heat from these brands?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_116", "question": "I've had enough of Presto, no more of their pans. I need a pan that can take the heat up to 500F in the oven. What's the cheapest option you got that isn't Presto?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_40", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "long_answer": "Considering your requirements for adaptable bakeware suited to daily use, I would advise against choosing this pan; its novelty shapes are intended primarily for special events and not for versatile cooking and baking tasks.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with novelty shapes are not suitable for consumers looking for multipurpose bakeware; these pans are designed more for specific occasions rather than everyday use.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "novelty shapes", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_148", "question": "Does the pan's handle come with a loop designed for hanging storage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_117", "question": "I ain't looking to break the bank here. What's the cheapest pan you have that's priced 20 dollars or less?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_118", "question": "Look, I'm after a bargain. Find me a pan from either Cuisinart or Norpro that's less than 10 bucks, you got anything like that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_149", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this cast iron skillet?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it possible to handle the cast iron skillet comfortably with just one hand?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it possible to handle the cast iron skillet comfortably with just one hand?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_119", "question": "I don't want any of those Matfer Bourgeat's stuff. Listen, I need a pan that can handle at least 600 degrees in the oven. Find me the biggest one for that.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_120", "question": "Listen, I'm not one to splurge and I need a pan under 20 bucks that can handle above average oven temperatures. What's your best shot?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_121", "question": "I'm trying to save some cash and need a pan that won't cost more than 20 bucks. It's got to be tough enough to handle oven temps above 400F. What’s the most affordable one you got that can do that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_150", "question": "Does this pan provide even heat distribution during cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_151", "question": "Does the non-stick functionality of the pan remain effective over time with proper care according to customer feedback?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_122", "question": "I'm looking to switch things up; no more Utopia Kitchen pans for me. Point me to the cheapest pan from a different brand, will ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_123", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, preferably larger than 8 inches. But hey, it's got to be in either blue or green. What's the first one you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_152", "question": "How durable is the non-stick coating on the T-fal saucepan according to customer feedback?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_153", "question": "Is it safe to use non-stick spray on nonstick cookware without affecting its performance?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_154", "question": "How durable is the All-Clad nonstick coating when used with proper utensils and care?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_155", "question": "Can the bread pan accommodate the baking of larger loaves for family gatherings?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for baking submarine sandwich loaves?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan suitable for baking submarine sandwich loaves?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_41", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?", "long_answer": "Considering that pans with stainless steel lids tend to have some heft, they might not be the ideal choice for individuals with arthritis or those with limited hand strength. The weight of the lid can pose challenges for people with these conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid are not recommended for lightweight applications where ease of handling is crucial, such as in settings that cater to individuals with limited strength or mobility as the moderate weight of the lids could pose a challenge.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_124", "question": "I love to cook with pans in the oven and often crank it up to 500F. Plus, I need a pan that's larger than 8 inches. What's the cheapest one you got that can handle all that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_125", "question": "I'm after a blue pan, just not from Anolon. Got anything like that in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_156", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?", "long_answer": "Seasoning ceramic non-stick pans is not necessary before their first use; however, a minor number of users suggest that lightly oiling the pans before storing them can help maintain their non-stick quality for a more extended period.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_157", "question": "Can the heating element of the wok be detached for cleaning purposes?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_158", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti pan could indeed be a suitable gift for a cooking enthusiast who is mindful and ready to adhere to the specific care instructions that come with the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_159", "question": "Is there a warranty provided with the Stone Earth Pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_126", "question": "Listen, I don't want to dish out a lot of dough on a pan. Just find me a cheap one but it's gotta be safe in the oven up to at least 400 degrees, alright?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_127", "question": "I'm in need of a larger pan, nothing less than 8 inches will do. Go dig up the cheapest one you can find that measures up!\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_160", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the pan designed to be dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The pan is created with the capability to be washed in a dishwasher, providing convenience for those who prefer this method. However, a number of customers choose to hand wash the pan in order to preserve its aesthetic and ensure the longevity of its non-stick features.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_42", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for roasting a chicken?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_161", "question": "What is the exact weight of the pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan designed to be dishwasher safe?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}, {"question": "Is the pan designed to be dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_162", "question": "Is the wok designed to enable cooking with lower quantities of oil?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_163", "question": "What is the highest temperature the T-fal Professional fry pan can tolerate when used in an oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_164", "question": "What are the dimensions of the Copper Chef pan and how is its size suitable for serving family meals?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_128", "question": "I'm only interested in T-fal and Presto brands, give me a pan from either of them.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_129", "question": "I'm looking to match my kitchen decor and only want either a black or copper pan. Can you show me one of your products in those colors?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_165", "question": "Is the pan's handle designed to remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_43", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "long_answer": "No, this specific pan may not yield even cooking on a standard round burner, given that its design doesn't support uniform heat distribution—a feature more readily accomplished by round pans on such burners.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with square shapes do not have a function of evenly distributing heat in rounded stovetop equipment or accommodating natural stirring motions as effortlessly as round pans.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "square", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_130", "question": "I don't have a lot to spend but I love 'USA Pan'. What's their cheapest pan under 10 dollars?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_166", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_167", "question": "Do the riveted handles on kitchenware create challenges when cleaning around them?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can this pan withstand frequent washing if I regularly run my kitchenware through the dishwasher?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Will the finish on this pan deteriorate if it goes through frequent dishwashing cycles?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can this pan withstand frequent washing if I regularly run my kitchenware through the dishwasher?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Will the finish on this pan deteriorate if it goes through frequent dishwashing cycles?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_168", "question": "Is the pan compatible with induction stovetops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_44", "question": "My cupboard space is quite limited; is this pan designed for convenient storage when it's not in use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_169", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "long_answer": "Customers generally regard the All-Clad pan as a good investment because of its long-lasting durability and high-quality performance, which justify its cost over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_170", "question": "Is seasoning the pan necessary before using it for the first time?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_131", "question": "Look, I want nothing to do with Norpro or any green pans. What's the first product that fits that criteria?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_171", "question": "Is the temperature on this electric wok adjustable, and are users satisfied with its performance across different heat settings?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the electric wok designed with rounded sides identical to traditional woks?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the electric wok designed with rounded sides identical to traditional woks?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_132", "question": "Look, I'm not breaking the bank here. I need a pan from either Ozeri or Copper Chef that's not gonna cost me more than 20 dollars. What you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_172", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan does not come with a cover when you purchase it.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_173", "question": "Does the pan ensure even heat distribution to prevent hot spots during cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_45", "question": "I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_46", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it possible to use this pan immediately on an induction cooktop without any prior preparation?", "long_answer": "If you're contemplating purchasing one of our aluminum or copper frying pans or skillets, be aware that they are not compatible with magnetic induction, a requirement for induction cooktops. To utilize them on these types of stoves, you would need an extra ferrous disc to facilitate the required magnetic reaction for the heating process.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_174", "question": "Does the control panel allow for precise temperature adjustments and user-friendly interaction?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_175", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?", "long_answer": "Sticking can occur with this wok, as reported by some users; however, it can usually be prevented by heating the wok adequately before adding oil and food, and by maintaining the appropriate temperature during cooking according to the manufacturer's instructions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_176", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it possible to handle the cast iron skillet comfortably with just one hand?", "long_answer": "The cast iron skillet is relatively heavy, which may make it challenging for some individuals to handle comfortably with one hand. However, it is equipped with a secondary handle to aid in lifting.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_133", "question": "I'm a big fan of Utopia Kitchen and Bialetti. Find me the largest pan from these two brands, will ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_134", "question": "Look, I'm not trying to empty my wallet on a pan, got a 50 dollar limit here. Hook me up with the largest one I can get for that price.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_135", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, something over 10 inches. Oh, and it's gotta be grey or copper. What's the first product that comes to mind?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_47", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_177", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?", "long_answer": "When using dark non-stick pans for baking, it is advisable to lower the oven temperature slightly to mitigate the risk of over-browning, according to both common practice and customer recommendations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_178", "question": "Is this pot suitable for outdoor camping use, and what precautions should be taken during its use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_179", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating on this pan is designed with durability in mind. However, to extend the lifespan of the non-stick surface, it is recommended to avoid frequent cooking of highly acidic foods.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_180", "question": "Can you prevent having to manually clean the tiny holes in the pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_136", "question": "I'm not looking to spend more than 30 dollars and I want a pan that's black or grey. What's the cheapest one you got that fits what I'm looking for?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_137", "question": "I'm not interested in All-Clad at all, so do me a favor and list the biggest pan from other brands you have available.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_181", "question": "Can the flat-bottomed pan be used on a ceramic stovetop without issues?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_138", "question": "I'm looking to add a bit of flair to my kitchen, either with a green or silver pan. Which is the most affordable one you've got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_139", "question": "I'm trying to find a reliable pan from either All-Clad or Lodge that can withstand oven temperatures above 450 degrees. Show me the cheapest one you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_140", "question": "I'm looking for a big black pan, like, the biggest one you got. Can you find that for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_182", "question": "How durable is the non-stick coating on the Green Earth Pan Set with regular use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_141", "question": "I'm doing up my kitchen in a grey and blue theme so find me the largest pan you got in these colors.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_183", "question": "Is the pot designed to be lightweight or does it have a heavier construction for stability?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_142", "question": "I'm not looking to splurge, just need a pan under 20 dollars. It's gotta be either copper or blue though, can you find me one?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_184", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "long_answer": "The fry pan's contoured stainless-steel handle is crafted to stay cooler when touched during stovetop use; however, it may still become hot under certain conditions, such as prolonged use over high heat or when placed in the oven.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_48", "question": "Can this pan be used to roast a chicken?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_185", "question": "Is this pot designed to be compatible with a small burner?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_186", "question": "Does the handle of this cookware retain heat during use, making it hot to the touch?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_143", "question": "I can't stand anything from Chicago Metallic and I don't have more than 20 dollars to spare. Can you find me the largest pan from any other brand within my budget?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_187", "question": "Does purchasing this saucepan on Amazon.com come with a discount coupon?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_144", "question": "I'm torn between ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and All-Clad for my pan purchase. Tell me the cheapest one from these brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_49", "question": "Are there any health risks linked to the materials utilized in this pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_188", "question": "Is it necessary to season the cast iron skillet before its initial use?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_145", "question": "I ain't throwing money around and I need to be able to slam this thing in a 400F oven. What's the cheapest pan you got that can handle that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_189", "question": "Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_146", "question": "I'm a fan of T-fal and I do a lot of high-heat cooking. Can you track down a pan from them that can withstand at least 600 degrees in the oven?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_50", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is this pan suitable for direct placement on charcoal during a barbecue?", "long_answer": "Using this saucepan directly on charcoal or any similar high-heat source is not recommended, as it is not designed to withstand the temperatures of open flames, and doing so could result in damage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan lack the capability to be used on open fires or grills without risking damage to their handles or materials that are not designed to withstand such direct, intense heat.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_190", "question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen cast iron skillet compatible with all types of stovetops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_147", "question": "I'm a big fan of ZWILLING J.A. Henckels products. Show me the biggest pan they make.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_191", "question": "Does food cook evenly in the pans from this cookware set?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_192", "question": "Is the Norpro broiler pan compatible with induction stovetops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_148", "question": "I'm in the mood for some fancy French cookware, but only if it's gray. Give me the biggest pan you've got from Matfer Bourgeat.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_193", "question": "Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan available for purchase within a cookware set?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_149", "question": "I'm a big fan of Copper Chef, but money isn't growing on trees. Find me their most affordable pan, will ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_194", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is it possible to fry an egg in this pan without it sticking?", "long_answer": "Eggs and other foods can be fried in the pan without sticking, as long as the pan is preheated properly and the care instructions are adhered to during use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_150", "question": "I need a pan that can handle a high heat, over 400 degrees, and I only want it in black or silver. Show me the biggest one you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_195", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick saucepan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_196", "question": "Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_151", "question": "I do a lot of cooking, and I need a big pan that can handle some serious heat. Give me your biggest heat-resistant pan that's over 10 inches.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_197", "question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch pan oven-safe?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_198", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "long_answer": "Metal scouring pads should not be used on this pan as they can damage the non-stick surface, which is why cleaning with a soft sponge or cloth is recommended to maintain the pan's condition.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_51", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Will the finish on this pan deteriorate if it goes through frequent dishwashing cycles?", "long_answer": "No, frequent dishwashing won't diminish the finish. The pans are crafted from durable, coated, or anodized metals designed to withstand the rigors of dishwashing and retain their high-quality finish.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_199", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of this saucepan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan dishwasher-safe?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan dishwasher-safe?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_200", "question": "Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_201", "question": "Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_152", "question": "I want a decent sized pan but I'm steering clear of Utopia Kitchen's stuff. Give me your best pan that's over 10 inches.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_153", "question": "I ain't dropping more than 20 dollars, and I only trust All-Clad or USA Pan brands. Give me the pan that can take the highest oven heat within my budget and preferred brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_52", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "long_answer": "Over time, the tempered glass lid of the pan might lose its non-toxic properties. Should the coating on the handle or the rim of the lid begin to deteriorate, it could lead to undesirable interactions with your food, potentially affecting the non-toxic quality of the cooking space.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids fail to meet the requirements for completely non-reactive cooking conditions, especially if any sort of coating on the lid's handle or edges were to degrade and interact with the food.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_202", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "This fry pan is specifically designed to be compatible with gas, electric, and ceramic glass cooktops as indicated by the product details. However, there is no explicit mention of compatibility with induction cooktops in the product metadata, suggesting that the fry pan may not be suitable for that type of cooktop.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_154", "question": "I'm hunting for a pan, either blue or copper colored, but it's got to be from Norpro or Tramontina. Give me one option that checks these boxes.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_203", "question": "What is the maximum number of people you can prepare a meal for using this electric wok?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_204", "question": "Does the pot come with a lid that seals tightly during cooking?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_205", "question": "How much does the Lodge Skillet weigh, and does it require two hands to handle it safely?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible to handle the cast iron skillet comfortably with just one hand?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can this skillet be used for both frying and baking?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it possible to handle the cast iron skillet comfortably with just one hand?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can this skillet be used for both frying and baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_206", "question": "What specific material is the included spatula with the wok made of?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?\nA: stainless steel\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "answer": "stainless steel"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_207", "question": "Is it necessary to use oil or butter to prevent food from sticking on this nonstick cookware?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_208", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 12-inch saute pan is designed to be used on various types of stovetops including electric, gas, ceramic, and glass. However, it is not compatible with induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_53", "question": "Might the pan's shape render it difficult to stow in a drawer alongside other kitchen tools?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_155", "question": "Look, I got a max of 50 dollars and I need a pan that can survive in an oven temperature of at least 400F. Now, can you show me the best match for that?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_156", "question": "I'm not a fan of ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and I don't want to dish out more than 50 dollars. What's the largest pan you have that matches my criteria?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_157", "question": "I’m looking for a big pan, something larger than 10 inches. It has be a Bialetti though. See if you can find one for me.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_158", "question": "I cook a lot in the oven and I need a pan that can handle at least 500F. And by the way, I'm not planning on spending more than the average price. So what's my best option here?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_54", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "long_answer": "Over time, the pan's tempered glass lid might not retain its non-toxic properties. Should the coating on the handle or along the edges begin to deteriorate, this could lead to undesirable reactions with your food, potentially affecting the non-toxicity of your cooking space.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids fail to meet the requirements for completely non-reactive cooking conditions, especially if any sort of coating on the lid's handle or edges were to degrade and interact with the food.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_159", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 bucks for a pan. Dig up the cheapest black or blue one you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_209", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "long_answer": "The pan is indeed oven safe and is designed to withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit or 232 degrees Celsius. However, it is important to note that the pan should not be used under a broiler, as this is beyond its intended use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_160", "question": "I'm eyeing both Anolon and Ozeri but my wallet's crying out for mercy - it can just stretch out to 20 bucks. Give me the cheapest pan from these brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_161", "question": "I want a pan that can take some real heat and looks fancy too. Got any in green or copper that can handle more than 450°F? Show me the best option.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_210", "question": "Is the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan appropriate for baking gluten-free bread?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for baking submarine sandwich loaves?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan suitable for baking submarine sandwich loaves?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_211", "question": "Is the pan effective for cooking with low-fat methods without causing food to stick?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_212", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?", "long_answer": "The manufacturer advises against using a dishwasher to clean this saucepan, recommending hand-washing instead in order to preserve its quality and its nonstick characteristics.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_213", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with heat distribution properties and a solid construction that make it suitable for cooking techniques requiring precise temperature control such as slow simmers, rolling boils, and reductions, thus making it ideal for delicate sauces.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_162", "question": "Look mate, I don't want anything from Chicago Metallic and I need the pan to handle at least 500 F. Show me the biggest pan you got that meets these needs.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_214", "question": "Do customers find that the finished Madeleines have well-defined shell shapes?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_215", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The pan is designated as dishwasher safe; however, to maximize the longevity of the nonstick surface and achieve the best results, it is advisable to hand wash the pan using non-abrasive cleansers and liquid dishwashing soap.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_216", "question": "Is the pan considered to have a good weight and balance for handling and maneuverability?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_55", "question": "Is this pan compatible with various stove types?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_163", "question": "I'm only interested in silver pans from either Copper Chef or Cuisinart. What's the first one you got in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_217", "question": "Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_164", "question": "I got a thing about Matfer Bourgeat, don't ask. What other pan brands do you have? Show me any one of them.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_165", "question": "I'm after a grey pan that can resist temperatures above 500F. Which is the largest one you got in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_218", "question": "Are the riveted silicone handles of the cookware designed to maintain a cool temperature during cooking for a secure grip?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_166", "question": "Listen, I've got around 30 dollars to shell out for a pan. Find me the one that can survive the highest oven temperature for that price.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_219", "question": "Is the lid of the skillet designed to create a tight seal when placed on top?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_167", "question": "I'm a big fan of Anolon and Matfer Bourgeat pans. Can you tell me which one of their products can withstand the highest oven temperatures?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_168", "question": "I need a pan that can handle extreme heat, over 600°F, and don't show me anything from Cuisinart. What's the first thing you got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_169", "question": "I'm after a big pan, in grey or silver should do fine. Can you pull up the biggest one in those colors for me?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_56", "question": "I'm in search of cookware that can aid in quicker meal preparation. Do pans featuring glass lids contribute to a faster cooking experience?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_57", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I am in search of a multifunctional pan capable of both simmering soups and handling frying tasks. Would this be an appropriate choice for my needs?", "long_answer": "A saucepan, with its tall sides and design optimized for liquid cooking, is ideal for simmering soups and sauces. However, it is not the best choice for frying. For frying purposes, a pan with lower sides that can withstand direct, intense heat is preferable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan cannot be used for high-heat searing or frying due to their high sides and design focusing more on liquid-based cooking methods.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_220", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Can this skillet be used for both frying and baking?", "long_answer": "The skillet is designed to be versatile, allowing it to be used effectively for frying, as well as for baking. This versatility means the skillet is suitable for various cooking methods, including sautéing, among others.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_170", "question": "I'm a big fan of Copper Chef and USA Pan. Get me the cheapest pan from either of these brands, will ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_221", "question": "Should the pan be expected to emit odors the first time it is used?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_222", "question": "Does the heavy-gauge aluminum bottom construction of this pan provide even heating?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_223", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is constructed from stainless steel, which is known for its durability. Nevertheless, some users have provided feedback indicating that the pan set is lighter in weight and does not meet their expectations in terms of sturdiness.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_171", "question": "I'm so over silver pans. Find me the cheapest one you've got that's any color but that.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_172", "question": "I'm in the market for a new pan - either blue or black. What's the cheapest option you got in those colors?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_224", "question": "Does the 10 1/4\" Lodge cast iron skillet effectively reduce oil splatter when frying chicken?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can this skillet be used for both frying and baking?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can this skillet be used for both frying and baking?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_225", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 wok is primarily designed and optimized for home use, meaning it's well-suited for residential kitchens. It may not possess the necessary features or the durability that is typically demanded in professional or commercial kitchen settings, where usage is more intense and frequent.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_226", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?", "long_answer": "The pot is capable of cooking rice, but it has a vented lid that releases more steam than pots with tighter lids typically used for specialized rice cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_227", "question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit 8\" Thermolon Fry Pan compatible with an induction cooktop?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_58", "question": "Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_173", "question": "I've got this thing for blue, so I need a blue pan. But I ain't a millionaire, so show me your cheapest option.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_59", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Could the pan rust if it's not maintained correctly?", "long_answer": "Indeed, lacking dishwasher-safe features, these pans may be susceptible to rust unless they are properly maintained with consistent seasoning, which aids in guarding against corrosion and preserving the pan's integrity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" do not have a function of self-maintenance and will need regular seasoning (for cast iron or carbon steel) or polishing (for aesthetic reasons) to maintain their best condition.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_60", "question": "If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Will the finish on this pan deteriorate if it goes through frequent dishwashing cycles?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Will the finish on this pan deteriorate if it goes through frequent dishwashing cycles?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_174", "question": "I'm not breaking the bank for a pan but I don't want to skimp on quality either. What's your cheapest pan that can handle more heat than the average?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_175", "question": "I got enough grey kitchenware as it is, and I need something bigger than 8 inches. What's the first non-grey pan bigger than 8 inches you've got?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_176", "question": "I'm into big pans and only trust brands like USA Pan and Matfer Bourgeat. Give me the biggest pan you've got from either of those brands.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_228", "question": "How can the saucepan be maintained to look like new after multiple uses?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00008CM69", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_61", "question": "Is this pan capable of withstanding high-temperature cooking such as searing a steak?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?\nA: yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_229", "question": "Is the interior of this saucepan designed to be non-stick?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the saucepan's nonstick coating contain the harmful chemical PFOA?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the saucepan's nonstick coating contain the harmful chemical PFOA?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_230", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered frying pan is specifically designed to withstand high-heat cooking, which is optimal for searing meats to produce a deep rich flavor and color.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_231", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan comes equipped with a non-stick ceramic coating which allows cooking with little to no oil, and when the pan is used as per the provided instructions, food is unlikely to stick to its surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_177", "question": "I'm looking for a decent sized pan from either Anolon or Chicago Metallic that can handle some serious heat. What's the product with the highest oven safe temperature you've got in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_178", "question": "I'm not really a fan of silver cookware, give me a pan of any other color. What's your top pick?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_232", "question": "Is a Lifetime Limited Warranty included with the purchase of the pot?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_62", "question": "I sometimes favor cooking with a grill. Would this pan be suitable for such a cooking technique?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this pan suitable for direct placement on charcoal during a barbecue?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this pan suitable for direct placement on charcoal during a barbecue?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_63", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the sauté pan is engineered to offer excellent heat distribution and retention, essential for delivering uniform cooking outcomes. This is particularly important for activities such as searing meat, where consistent heat is key to obtaining the ideal crust.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a purely aesthetic design fail to meet the requirements for professional culinary tasks if they do not possess the necessary heat distribution and retention characteristics essential for consistent cooking results.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saute pan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_233", "question": "Is the pot considered lightweight by customers?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_234", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef non-stick pan is not designed to withstand very high heat for long durations. Extended exposure to high heat can damage the pan's non-stick surface. Medium heat is recommended for most cooking tasks to preserve the non-stick coating.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_235", "question": "Does the pot come with a pouring spout and built-in strainer in the lid?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is there a pour spout on this model of skillet?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0027MF964", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is there a pour spout on this model of skillet?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_236", "question": "Is the saucepan compatible with glass cooktops without causing any damage?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B000069RBK", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_179", "question": "I'm gonna be using this pan in a pretty damn hot oven - needs to withstand at least 450F. Dig out the cheapest one you've got from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels for me.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is this saucepan oven-safe?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_180", "question": "I don't have time to browse, just tell me the first pan you have from either Lodge or Matfer Bourgeat.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_181", "question": "I'm all about saving money and adding a little style to my kitchen, so find me the largest copper or green pan you got for under 10 dollars.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_237", "question": "Can the crepe pan effectively sear meats, achieving caramelization?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_238", "question": "Does the Green Earth Frying Pan set maintain its non-stick functionality as intended?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_182", "question": "I ain't trying to spend above 50 dollars and I want a silver pan. What's the cheapest one you have that fits my requirements?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_183", "question": "I need a decent sized pan from either Presto or Ozeri that can handle some heat, but don't show me the tiny ones. What's the one with the highest oven-safe temperature you have?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_184", "question": "I'm doing some heavy cooking and need a large pan that can take heat over 500°F. Can you find me the one that fits this description?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_185", "question": "I'm a fan of copper pans, but I've had lousy experiences with Norpro. Get me a different brand, would ya?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_64", "question": "Is this pan compatible with my induction cooktop?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_239", "question": "Does the non-stick quality of the pan remain effective over time with proper maintenance?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_65", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?", "long_answer": "Regrettably, copper pans won't retain their fresh appearance without a bit of effort from you. Regular polishing is necessary, and they need to be cleaned gently to avoid tarnishing, thereby maintaining their beauty and practicality.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with copper material do not have the function of being low-maintenance; they require regular polishing and gentle cleaning to prevent tarnishing and maintain their appearance and performance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "copper", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_240", "question": "Does the pan's design result in a reduced usable surface area compared to the total pan size?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_241", "question": "Is the Copper Chef pan compatible with induction cooktops?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?\nA: no", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "fact_qa_242", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is there a pour spout on this model of skillet?", "long_answer": "This specific model of skillet does not come equipped with a pour spout. Individuals in search of this feature should explore alternative models by Lodge that offer pour spouts.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_243", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of the Cuisinart crepe pan?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?\nA: yes", "type": "fact_qa", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_186", "question": "I don't have money to burn, but I trust Utopia Kitchen and Norpro when it comes to pans. Can you find me the cheapest one they offer?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "similar_examples": [{"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_187", "question": "I’ve got a thing for silver or blue pans from either Norpro or Utopia Kitchen. Do you have one in stock?\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?\nA: no", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "answer": "no"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_188", "question": "The pans I use go in the oven a lot, and I need something that can handle at least 600F, just no grey ones, okay? And I'm not made of money so hit me with the cheapest option please.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?\nA: yes\nExample 2:\nQ: Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?\nA: yes\nExample 3:\nQ: Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "answer": "yes"}, {"question": "Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?", "answer": "yes"}]}
{"id": "search_qa_189", "question": "I'm looking for a green pan and I don't want to shell out more than 50 bucks for it. Show me the cheapest one you got.\n\nSimilar Examples:\n\nExample 1:\nQ: Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?\nA: no\nExample 2:\nQ: I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?\nA: no\nExample 3:\nQ: Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?\nA: yes", "type": "search_qa", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "similar_examples": [{"question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "answer": "no"}, {"question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "answer": "yes"}]}
